

## SHRIKANT B. AUTI

Software Sales Professional

Accomplished sales professional with 7 years of experience in winning large deals independently, working with cross functional teams to execute projects, achieving sales quota and contribute to regional growth. Effectively penetrated new verticals and ensured revenue generation.

shrikantauti@ymail.com

Tirupati Complex, Plot No. 7 & 8, Sector No. 36, Wing A, Flat No. 603, Mansarovar, Mansarovar, Navi Mumbai, INDIA

9870223602

linkedin.com/in/shriauti

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Enterprise Sales Manager Ingenico ePayments India Pvt. Ltd.

09/2018 - Present Mumba

Global leader in payment processing. Products - Payment Gateway, Recurring Payments (Online and Offline), LinkPay, Account Validation.

KRA & Achievements

- Responsible for Net New, Cross Sell revenue from West region of India.
- Acquired large accounts in NBFC, FinTech, Insurance, Education and NGO vertices.
- Managed existing Government accounts. Cross sold various payment modes to increase wallet share.
- Achievements: Acquired 7 New Logos. Cross sold services to existing accounts, thereby revenue increment grew by 270%.

# **Business Development Manager**Proteus Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

03/2013 - 08/2018 Mumbai

Part of parent company Base Information Management Pvt. Ltd., renowned software provider for Pharma. Products - ERP, SFA, CRM, IBM Cognos BI, SaaS

KRA & Achievements

- Responsible for Net New revenue from Mumbai and Pune region.
- Handled end to end sales cycle i.e. Prospecting, Requirement Gathering, Demonstration, Commercial Negotiation, Closure and Account Management.
- Selling Turnkey assignments, Value Added Services to customers as a Cross Sell offering. Signed AMCs at enhanced rate YOY.
- Working with digital marketing team to develop Case Studies.
  Product exhibition at various exhibitions and events.
- Achievements: Over achieved sales target 140% YOY, Won deals in FMCG space, an unexplored vertical for the company.

#### **EDUCATION**

Master of Business Administration, Marketing Sikkim Manipal University Distance Education

03/2012 - 05/2014 First Class

**B.Sc. Information Technology** Mumbai University

#### **SKILLS**

Account Management	• • • • •
Consultative Selling	• • • • •
Revenue Enhancement	• • • • •
Competitive Intelligence	• • • • •
Customer Relationship Management	• • • • •
Territory Management	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$
Channel Management	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$
Team Management	• • • • •

#### **LANGUAGES**

English Hindi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Marathi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### **INTERESTS**

Movies: Big fan of Drama, Thriller genres.

Reading: Autobiography - Technological, Historical, Political greats; Fiction & Non Fiction.

Sports: Passionate about Test Cricket. Represented at inter school and college level.

Music: Enjoy listening to instrumental music, orchestra.

08/2008 - 08/2011 First Class